https://www.astronics.com/privacy-policy

Aircraft Data Systems
Aircraft Interface Devices (AID)
Cockpit Controls & Panels
Helicopter Emergency Egress Lighting (HEEL)
Privacy Policy
Privacy PolicyAstronics is committed to protecting any personal information that you may provide to us. In particular, we believe it is important for you to know how we treat information about you that we may receive from this website.Information CollectedUse of Collected InformationLinks to Other SitesSecurity of Collected InformationChildren Under the Age of 13Access to Collected InformationContacting UsChanges to this PolicyInformation CollectedIn general, you can visit this website without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself. Our web servers collect the domain names, not the e-mail addresses, of visitors. Our web servers also seek (as many websites do) to place
“cookies” (small data files) on your computer's hard drive, which allow the server to determine the computer when it visits again, in order to track statistical information about navigation to and throughout certain areas of our site and
to provide an efficient customer experience. The information that is tracked is used only for internal purposes, such as to improve site navigation, improve your experience with us, and to measure the effectiveness of our promotional placements. This
information is not shared with anyone other than Astronics affiliates and contractors who assist Astronics in these efforts and are bound to confidentiality. Like many websites, we do not currently respond to “do not track” browser headers.
If you prefer not to accept cookies, you decline our cookie notice and can set your browser to reject them or to alert you before one is placed.In addition, there are portions of this website where we may need to collect personal information from you for a specific purpose, such as to provide you with information you request. The information collected from you may include your name, address,
telephone, fax number, e-mail address, and the nature of your request, such as a product inquiry or newsletter subscription.Use of Collected InformationInitial domain name information that we collect is not used to personally identify you and instead is aggregated to measure the number of visits, average time spent on the site, pages viewed, etc. We use this information to measure the use of our site
and to improve the content of our site.Should you choose to share other information with us, such as your name and e-mail address, we generally let you know at the time of collection how we will use the personal information, and your information may be matched to your domain name. Usually,
we use the personal information you provide only to respond to your inquiry or to process your request (such as to receive electronic annual reports or to be added to our supplier diversity database). Should you elect to subscribe to our newsletter,
we will send you periodic updates on new products, events, articles, and other happenings.We may share the personal information you provide with other companies, both inside and outside of the U.S., we have hired to provide services for us, such as a sales distributor or email service provider. These companies - our vendors - are contractually
bound to use personal information we share with them only to perform the services we have hired them to provide. We do not share, sell, or lease personal information about you to any third-parties for their marketing use. We will release information
about you if you direct us to do so, if we are required by law to do so, or in other legally limited circumstances (for example, to protect your account from fraud).If you share your personal information with us, we keep it for the length of time necessary. For some of our customers on long-term programs, this can mean we will keep your information for years. We periodically review this information and delete contacts
with little or no engagement after certain periods of time.Links to Other SitesAstronics' website may contain links to other sites. While we try to link only to sites that share our high standards and respect for privacy, we are not responsible for the content, security, or privacy practices employed by other sites.Security of Collected InformationWe maintain strict physical, electronic, and administrative safeguards to protect your personal information from unauthorized or inappropriate access. We restrict access to information about you to those who need to know the information to respond to
your inquiry or request. Anyone who misuses personal information is subject to disciplinary action.Children Under the Age of 13Astronics’ website is not intended for children under 13 years of age. No one under age 13 may provide any information to or on the website. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If you are under 13, do not use
or provide any information on this website or on or through any of its features/register on the website, make any purchases through the website or provide any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, e-mail
address or any screen name or user name you may use. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information
from or about a child under 13, please use the Site Feedback link in the footer.Access to Collected InformationYou may request to review and update the information that you provide to us through this website by contacting us as described below.Contacting UsIf you have any questions about this privacy policy, please use the Site Feedback link in the website footer section below. We welcome your questions and suggestions about our privacy policy.Changes to this PolicyPlease check this privacy policy periodically to inform yourself of any changes. Although we reserve the right to modify or supplement this privacy policy, we will provide notice to you on this website of any major changes for at least 30 days following
the change.
Products & Solutions Aircraft Data Systems Aircraft Electrical Power Systems Custom Design & Manufacturing Emergency Systems Enhanced Vision Systems IFC Antennas and Radome Systems Inflight Entertainment System Hardware Instrumentation Interiors & Structures Lighting Systems Seat Actuation Systems Simulation & Training Systems Certification Test & Measurement VIP IFEC & CMS Systems View All Products
Subsidiaries Astronics Advanced Electronic Systems Astronics AeroSat Astronics Ballard Technology Astronics Connectivity Systems and Certification Astronics Custom Control Concepts Astronics DME Astronics Luminescent Systems Inc Astronics PECO Inc Astronics PGA Astronics Test Systems View All Subsidiaries
FAQS CONTACT US SITE FEEDBACK
Sign Up for Astronics Email
Privacy Policy |
Legal | Terms Of Use
© 2020 Astronics Corporation. All rights reserved.
